Sirens scream, but I don't hear a thing.
Clipboards and contracts they try to bring.
Hands reaching out like I'm some kind of case.
But my answer's written all over my face.
Your statement is a paper disguise.
I've read of all that swallow the mice.
D and I need just a quart, just let me be.
The rest of the day, don't bless me, don't fix me.
I won't sign a point for it if you sip on pee.
D and I need, D and I need.
Said he'd breathe, way late, oh oh.
Now he runs in this show.
You chase me down with your answers and meds.
Rectate men, that has just been in my head.
Don't call my name like I need to be fixed.
Don't write me off with your stat treats and tricks.
You've got your lists and your boss and your savior plans.
But it'll burn another day just like where I stand.
D and I need you at the court, just let me be.
The list has a date, don't risk it, don't fix me.
I won't sign your plight, for I know you'll sit by fee.
D and I need, D and I need.
Set me free, free me, oh oh.
Now I'm here, I'll beat myself.
Baby, oh oh.
TNR just let me know.